Bonowitz, Abraham J.; Papers apap186
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (NCADP), 1987-2015; 6; 2.8 cubic ft.
  - Abolution Rising, The Preeminent Annual Conference Program, ca. 2006 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 3)
  - "Abolution 2025 Campaign: September 2010 Strategy Update with Priorities" *RESTRICTED*, 2010 October 22 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 4)
  - Abolution Directory, ca. 2002 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 5)
  - Abolution Directory, ca. 2003 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 6)
  - Abolution Directory, ca. 2004 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 7)
  - Abolution Leadership Training Institute (ALTI) Agenda, Participants List & Goals, 2012 November 16-18 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 8)
  - Abolutionist Leadership Training Institute (ALTI) Application - Arkansas, 2008 August (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 9)
  - Abolutionist Leadership Training Institute (AlTI) Application - Connecticut, 2008 August (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 10)
  - Abolutionist Leadership Training Institute (ALTI) Application - Indiana, 2008 August (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 11)
  - Abolutionist Leadership Training Institute (ALTI) Application - Kansas, 2008 August (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 12)
  - Abolutionist Leadership Training Institute (ALTI) Application - Kentucky, 2008 August (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 13)
  - Abolutionist Leadership Training Institute (ALTI) Application - Missouri, 2008 August (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 14)
  - Abolitionist Leadership Training Institute (ALTI) Application - Mississippi, 2008 August (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 15)
  - Abolitionist Leadership Training Institute (ALTI) Application - New Hampshire, 2008 August (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 16)
  - Abolitionist Leadership Training Institute (ALTI) Application - New Mexico, 2008 August (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 17)
  - Abolitionist Leadership Training Institute (ALTI) Application - New York, 2008 August (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 18)
  - Abolitionist Leadership Training Institute (ALTI) Application - North Carolina, 2008 August (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 19)
  - Abolitionist Leadership Training Institute (ALTI) Application - Ohio, 2008 August (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 20)
  - Abolitionist Leadership Training Institute (ALTI) Application - Oregon, 2008 August (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 21)
  - Abolitionist Leadership Training Institute (ALTI) Application - Pennsylvania, 2008 August (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 22)
  - Abolitionist Leadership Training Institute (ALTI) Application - South Carolina, 2008 August (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 23)
  - Abolitionist Leadership Training Institute (ALTI) Application - Tennessee, 2008 August (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 24)
  - Abolitionist Leadership Training Institute (ALTI) Application - Texas, 2008 August (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 25)
  - Abolitionist Leadership Training Institute (ALTI) Application - Virginia, 2008 August (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 26)
  - Abolitionist Leadership Training Institute (ALTI) Catholic University of America - Final Report, 2008 August (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 27)
  - ALTI Contact List, 2008 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 28)
  - ALTI Evaluation, 2011 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 29)
  - ALTI Group Photos, 2008; 2009 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 30)
  - ALTI Planning Materials, 2008 August (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 31)
  - ALTI Planning Materials, 2009 August 1-3 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 32)
  - ALTI Summary Evaluations, 2008 August 6-8 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 33)
  - ALTI Training Staff Meetings, 2009 July 7 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 34)
  - Ad Hoc Meeting Agenda, 2008 October 22 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 35)
  - Affiliate Conference Call Schedule, 2010 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 36)
  - Affiliate Information Update Form, 2002 January 28 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 37)
  - Affiliate Publicity Guide, Undated (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 38)
  - Affiliate Resources on SHARC, Undated (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 39)
  - Affiliate Support Report, 2009 September 19 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 40)
  - Agenda for the Board Meeting, 2005 October 28 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 41)
  - Agenda at a Glance, 2011 November 18 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 42)
  - Annual Conference Evaluation Form, 2010 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 43)
  - Annual Conference Planning Materials, 2008 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 44)
  - Annual Conference Planning Meeting, 2009 March 25 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 45)
  - Annual Conference Program, 2004 October 14-17 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 46)
  - Annual Conference Organizing Meeting, 2005 September 12 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 47)
  - Annual Conference Schedule at a Glance, 2010 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 48)
  - Conference Training for the Long Run: Building Momentum for Repeal from January 13-16, 2011, 2011 June 18 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 49)
  - Annual Conference Work Plan, 2009 January 15-18 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 50)
  - Application for Affiliate Status, 2011 May 3; 2011 May 5 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 51)
  - Awards Book, 2009 December 28 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 52)
  - Award Winners, 1987-2009 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 53)
  - Board of Directors Material and Affiliate Information, 2004 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 54)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Materials, 2004-2005 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 55)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 2004 January 16 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 56)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Materials & Notes, 2005 July 24 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 57)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Materials & Notes, 2007 April 28 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 58)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Packets, 2007 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 59)
  - Board of Directors Report: Baseline Assistance Technical Support and Training by Aimee M. Gabel, 2009 May (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 60)
  - Board of Directors Report: Baseline Assistance Technical Support and Training, 2009 September (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 61)
  - Board Meeting Agenda and Materials, 2007 April (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 62)
  - Board Meeting Agenda and Materials, 2008 January 20 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 63)
  - Board Meeting Agenda and Materials, 2009 September 19 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 64)
  - Board Meeting Agenda and Materials, 2009 May 30 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 65)
  - Board Meeting Agenda and Presentation Slides, 2012 September (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 66)
  - Board Meeting Materials, 2006 January (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 67)
  - Board Meeting Materials, 2006 March (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 68)
  - Board Meeting Materials, 2007 November 10 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 69)
  - Board Meeting Materials and Notes, 2006 April (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 70)
  - Board Meeting Materials and Notes, 2007 January 20 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 71)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 2006 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 72)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 2007 April 28 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 73)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 2009 September 19 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 74)
  - Board Meeting Minutes and Agenda, 2008 September 13 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 75)
  - Board Meeting Minutes and Notes, 2004-2005 (Box 1 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 76)
  - Board Meeting Minutes and Materials, 2009 May (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 1)
  - Board Member Meeting Minutes and Notes, 2008 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 2)
  - Board Meeting Minutes and Notes, 2010 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 3)
  - Board Meeting Notes, 2006 January 21 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 4)
  - Board Member Ballot, Undated (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 5)
  - Bonowitz, Abraham's NCADP Speech, Undated (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 6)
  - Bonowitz, Abraham Employee Benefits Packet, 2009 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 7)
  - Bonowitz, Abraham, 2013 June 2013 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 8)
  - Bonowitz, Abraham Notes, ca. 2013 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 9)
  - Bonowitz, Abraham Cover Letter for Senior Project Manager or Senior Organizer at the Center for Community Change, 2013 July 13 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 10)
  - Bonowitz, Abraham's Request for Leave, 2013 June 13 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 11)
  - Bonowitz, Abraham Separation Agreement and General Release, 2013 July 8 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 12)
  - Budget Narrative Draft, 2004 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 13)
  - Building Communities of Justice and Hope, 25th Anniversary National Conference - Raleigh, North Carolina, 2001 October 18-21 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 14)
  - "Case for Success", Undated (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 15)
  - Catholic Universary of America Conference Planning Materials, 2008 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 16)
  - Candidates for the Board of Directors Statesments of Interest and Biographies, ca. 2004 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 17)
  - Committee Assignments, ca. 2004 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 18)
  - Communication, Lobbying and Development Strategies, 2006 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 19)
  - Communications Affinity Group Media Analysis, 2011 December 12 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 20)
  - Conference Call Agenda, 2010 January 7 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 21)
  - Conference Call: How Social Media Builds Affiliate Peer Conservation Evaluation, 2010 June 8 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 22)
  - Conference Notes, 2008 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 23)
  - Conference Planning Spreadsheet, 2010 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 24)
  - Conference Postcard, Undated (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 25)
  - Conference Registration, 2010 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 26)
  - Conference Report, 2003 November 21 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 27)
  - Conference Staff Responsibilities and Timeline, 2009 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 28)
  - Conference Tracks and Schedule for "Turning Wins Into Winning", 2005 October (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 29)
  - Conference, "Turning Wins Into Winning" - Austin, Texas Organizing Materials, 2005 October (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 30)
  - Conference Update, 2005 April 18 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 31)
  - Congratulations to Abe Bonowitz for Being Chosen As Abolitionist of the Year by the National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty from the Sppencer Group, Undated (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 32)
  - Coordinators Training Working Against the Death Penalty: How We Can Do It Better, 2005 July 22 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 33)
  - Council of Affiliates 2004 Year in Review, ca. 2004 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 34)
  - Dave Atwood Scholarship, 2010 March (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 35)
  - "Death Decision: Killer's Execution Scheduled by Glenn Pruit, 2004 March 23 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 36)
  - The Death Penalty and International Law, Undated (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 37)
  - Death Penalty National Coordination, Report *RESTRICTED*, 2013 June (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 38)
  - Deborah T. Portiz Bio, Undated (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 39)
  - Definining Your Strategic Plan II - Presentation by John D. Baker, ca. 2008 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 40)
  - Department of Affiliate Support Report to the Board of Directors, 2010 January 17 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 41)
  - "Detterence Report National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty", 2008 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 42)
  - Director of Affiliate Support Job Discription, 2010 March 9 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 43)
  - "Dollars and Doughnuts: An Interactive Discussion with NCADP Affiliates on Fundraising", Undated (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 44)
  - Draft of Bylaws of NCADP, 2006 July 27 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 45)
  - Draft - "Changing the Death Penalty Paradigm Through Rachel's Fund" by Diann Rust-Tierney, Undated (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 46)
  - Draft - National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty 1st Annual Abolitionist Leadership Training Institute, 2008 August 6-8 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 47)
  - Draft - Political Assessment Outline, 2008 July 2 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 48)
  - Email from Diann Rust-Tierney to Abraham Bonowitz About Hugo Adam Bedau's Death, 2012 August 17 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 49)
  - Emails on National RJA Petition, 2012 June 27 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 50)
  - Employees Benefits Proposal, 2002 January 31 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 51)
  - Executive Director's First Quarter Report, 2006 April 17 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 52)
  - First Annual Abolitionist Leadership Training Institute, 2008 August 6-8 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 53)
  - First Annual Abolitionist Leadership Training Institute Photo, 2008 August 6-8 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 54)
  - Five Year Strategic Plan, Undated (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 55)
  - Field & Communications Report, 2010 September 25; 2011 May 14 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 56)
  - Financial Report Summary, 2009 July (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 57)
  - "Framing the Message" by Shari Silberstein, Equal Justice USA Handout, ca. 2010 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 58)
  - Friday Evening Program, Undated (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 59)
  - Fundraising Plan of Action, 1992 January 6 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 60)
  - "Getting to 'Campaign 2.0' Findings and Recommendations for Improving the National Coalition for the Death Penalty Abolition, Conducted for the Abolition 2025 Steering Committee *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 61)
  - Grant Application Form, 2010 February 10 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 62)
  - Help Stop Virginia's 100th Execution - Email from Abraham Bonowitz, 2008 June 17 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 63)
  - "Human Rights, Human Wrongs, Sentencing Children to Death" National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 2003 March (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 64)
  - HBCU Tour, 2004 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 65)
  - "The Impact of Homocide on Families of Murder Victims" Rachel's Fund, 2010 September (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 66)
  - Information on Letters of Inquiry, 2009 March (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 67)
  - Innocent and Executed: Four Chapters in the Life of America's Death Penalty, 2007 February (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 68)
  - Intern Responsibilities, Undated (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 69)
  - The Kairos Conference - Atlanta, Georgia, 2010 November 16-17 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 70)
  - "Lay of the Land Political Assessment Tool", Undated (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 71)
  - Leadership Summit Planning Meeting, 1999 June 5 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 72)
  - Letter From Abraham Bonowitz to Abolitionists with List of How You Can Make A Difference, Undated (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 73)
  - Letter to Affiliates, 2008 February 29 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 74)
  - Letter to Affiliate Members, ca. 2004 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 75)
  - Letter from Diann Rust Tierney, Executive Director NCADP about Alberto Gonzales, 2005 January 26 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 76)
  - Letter from Diann Tust- Tierney to Abraham Bonowitz, 2005 March 18 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 77)
  - Letter from James E. Rocap, Board Chair Regarding Teresa Lewis, 2015 November 24 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 78)
  - Letter to NCADP from Pennsylvanians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, 2009 March 4 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 79)
  - List of Intensive States with Notes, Undated (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 80)
  - Lifelines Newsletter [1 of 2], 1999-2012 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 81)
  - Lifelines Newsletter [2 of 2], 1999-2012 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 82)
  - Lifelines State, Volume 2, Number 1, 2008 February 1 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 83)
  - Lifetime Achievement Award (Posthumous) to Rachel King, Undated (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 84)
  - "Maryland is a Bellwether for the Country or the Death Penalty" Flyer, Undated (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 85)
  - Master List of Affiliates and Potential Affiliates, 2009 February (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 86)
  - Meeting with Abe Bonowitz Regarding Expectations in Areas of Serious Concern, 2012 October 19 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 87)
  - Minutes of Board Meeting, 2006 April 22; 2006 July 29 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 88)
  - Minutes and Notes, 2010 September - 2011 March (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 89)
  - Meeting Notes, 2008 January (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 90)
  - Membership Factsheets with Corrections, Undated (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 91)
  - Memorandum: To Bonowitz, Abraham from Diann Rust-Tierney Acceptance of Resignation, 2013 June 26 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 92)
  - Memo: Feedback on NCADP Training Program, 2011 June 1 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 93)
  - Memo: Proposed Outline for Strategic Planning Process, 2005 January 28 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 94)
  - Memo: Roper v. Simmons: Summary, Effect, Messaging and Next Steps, 2005 March 4 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 95)
  - Memo: Staff Changes from Diann Rust-Tierney, 2005 February 9 (Box 2 (6-National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty (N), Folder 96)